// This file exports the array of quiz questions.
// You can add as many question objects as you like here.

const { quote } = require("discord.js");

module.exports = [
    {
        question: "What year was the Jurassic World server created?",
        options: ["2020", "2021", "2022", "2023", "2024", "2025"],
        correct: ["2021"],
    },
    {
        question: "Who made the lore of the JW server?",
        options: ["Berlin", "Lost", "Bridge", "Trivago"],
        correct: ["Bridge"],
    },
    {
        question:
            "What's the name of the cult thats celebrated during October that Blazing made??",
        options: ["Kill Crystal Club", "Jefftober", "White Darius Cult", "E"],
        correct: ["Jefftober"],
    },
    {
        question: "What level do you need to be a predator",
        options: ["10", "15", "25", "50"],
        correct: ["25"],
    },
    {
        question: "Who is the owner of the server?",
        options: ["Blazing", "Trivago", "Dogdson", "Blazing's alt"],
        correct: ["Blazing"],
    },
    {
        question: "The youngest member percentile in the server?",
        options: [
            "25% of the server",
            "50% of the server",
            "75% of the server",
            "100% of the server",
        ],
        correct: [
            "25% of the server",
            "50% of the server",
            "75% of the server",
            "100% of the server",
        ],
    },
    {
        question: "solve for: (4^3) + 3",
        options: ["63", "65", "67", "69"],
        correct: ["67"],
    },
    {
        question: "Who is the 2nd in command of the server?",
        options: ["Monty", "Trivago", "Nexat", "DOtson"],
        correct: ["Trivago"],
    },
    {
        question: "Who is the most unfunniest person in the server?",
        options: ["Crystal", "Berlin"],
        correct: ["Crystal", "Berlin"],
    },
    {
        question: "The weirdest member?",
        options: ["Crystal"],
        correct: ["Crystal"],
    },
    {
        question: "The most mentally insane mod?",
        options: ["crystal", "monty", "blazing", "trivago"],
        correct: ["crystal"],
    },
    {
        question: "Most unemployed member",
        options: ["Crystal", "Head of Ingen", "Blazing", "Berlin"],
        correct: ["Head of Ingen", "Crystal"],
    },
    {
        question: "which Member would get arrested for doing dumb shit",
        options: ["Monty", "Crystal", "Berlin", "Trivago"],
        correct: ["Monty", "Crystal"],
    },
    {
        question: "Who uses chat revive for random stuff?",
        options: ["Monty"],
        correct: ["Monty"],
    },
    {
        question: "who the Gayest person in the server?",
        options: ["crystal", "monty"],
        correct: ["monty"],
    },
    {
        question: "what is Crystals gender? (wrong answer will be banned)",
        options: ["gay", "boy", "ben", "girl?"],
        correct: ["gay"],
    },
    {
        question: "dino that is most talked about in the server?",
        options: ["spino", "rex", "trike", "insert rando dino name"],
        correct: ["spino"],
    },
    {
        question: "Who that one kid always cryin ab bein muted for a week?",
        options: ["berlin"],
        correct: ["berlin"],
    },
    {
        question: "Most Strict Mod?",
        options: ["dr.wu", "Nexat", "dosdgon", "ace"],
        correct: ["Nexat"],
    },
    {
        question: "most chronically online member?",
        options: ["blazing", "monty", "void", "crystal"],
        correct: ["crystal"],
    },
    {
        question: "member with most warns?",
        options: ["ziegler", "bridge", "berlin", "idk"],
        correct: ["ziegler"],
    },

    {
        question: "What typa server is the JW server",
        options: [
            "mental asylum",
            "rainbows and sunshine",
            "degen hell",
            "autistic",
        ],
        correct: ["mental asylum", "degen hell", "autistic"],
    },
    {
        question: "What rank is the user who is level 67?",
        options: ["Hunter", "Predator", "Apex predator", "Dominator"],
        correct: ["Apex predator"],
    },
];
